[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What city is the movie My Big Fat Greek Wedding set in?", "correct_answer": "Chicago", "incorrect_answers": ["Montreal", "Philidelphia", "New York"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the role of Zelma Bullock in Whats Love Got to Do With It?", "correct_answer": "Jennifer Lewis", "incorrect_answers": ["Anna Maria Horsford", "Loretta Divine", "Sandra Reaves-Phillips"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Scorpions are not found naturally in this geographical area.", "correct_answer": "New Zealand", "incorrect_answers": ["Australia", "Europe", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these actors set a record for most Best Actor Oscar nominations without winning?", "correct_answer": "Peter OToole", "incorrect_answers": ["Paul Newman", "Fredric March", "Spencer Tracy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the consumption of plant material by carnivores?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Carnivores consume feces of herbivores to get nutrients.", "Carnivores consume some plant material in order to get minerals, vitamins and fiber.", "Carnivores ingest the plant material the need along with their herbivorous prey."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The modern game of chess originated from this Indian game of strategy.", "correct_answer": "chaturanga", "incorrect_answers": ["sankara", "parchana", "mancala"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the horror film \u201cCarrie\u201d first hit the movie theatres?", "correct_answer": "1976", "incorrect_answers": ["1973", "1979", "1977"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of coat do beagles have?", "correct_answer": "medium", "incorrect_answers": ["long", "short", "depends on the dog"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Can tigers swim up to 4 miles?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the former Cheers characters is in the movie Benny and Joon as Bennys friend Thomas?", "correct_answer": "Dan Hedaya", "incorrect_answers": ["George Wendt", "Ted Danson", "Woody Harrelson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Say Anything, Diane is afraid of flying.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these words refers to secret and illegal production of whiskey, commonly carried out at night.", "correct_answer": "Moonshining", "incorrect_answers": ["Moonscape", "Moonbeam", "Moonstone"]}]